Salah Monzoor

404-369-9850 • Lawrenceville, GA • Salmonzoor@gmail.com https://github.com/salzm

OBJECTIVE

Associate-level professional trained in project management with 3 years + years professional experience in leading projects, presenting to clients & internal teams, time management, and working in sprints using Agile methodology. Looking for a role in Technical Project Management, Web Development, and/or Business Analyst.

EXPERIENCE

Randstad USA July 2023 - Present

IT Administrator Canon USA

- Tasked for ensuring project operations were satisfied and that internal team communication was handled appropriately
- Ensure that shipment and delivery is properly handled and customer's are answered.

CORL Technologies

October 2021 - February 2023

Business Analyst

- Tasked for ensuring project operations were satisfied and that internal team communication was handled appropriately
- Created business workflow processes using LucidChart to improve organizational structure inside the company.

Project Manager of Operations

- Coordinated communication with clients and vendors ensured confidentiality and integrity procedures, including weekly calls to assess vendors via security questionnaires.
- To make sure that the processes are moving ahead, SLA dates are fulfilled, and if necessary, escalation on the customer's behalf, PowerBI was used to present vendor data to the client.
- Made sure that Security Compliance was addressed and managed appropriately between clients and vendors.

Passio Technologies

September 2021- October 2021

Customer Support Representative/ Project Manager | Atlanta, Ga

- Handled problems involving troubleshooting hardware devices, software bug fixes, JSON errors on user accounts, customer inquiries, setting up meetings and client training, etc.
- Was one of the few staff members that were flown out on the company's dime along with the SQL engineer to identify and address a persistent problem with a devoted client.

Georgia State University Cyber Security Department of Research

January 2020 - May 2020

Project Team Lead | Atlanta, Ga

- Microsoft Project was used to keep track of the project's status, deadlines, and to keep the team focused on meeting client and deadline expectations.
- The CyberSecurity department of Georgia State achieved a 45% increase in compliance, educating staff and faculty on phishing, DDOS, DOS, scam emails, avoiding hacking, preventing information leaks, safe usage of public Wi-Fi, and related guidelines.

Delivery Comparisons Project

November 2019-December 2019

Front End Developer | Atlanta, Ga

- Web scraping was used to gather information from online pages in order to create a website that displayed the lowest prices from GrubHub, Uber Eats, and DoorDash.
- Supervised the website's UI design and developed it using HTML, CSS, and Javascript.

EDUCATION

Georgia Tech Web Development Bootcamp

March 2023 - June 20 2023

- Became proficient in Github, Git, branching on Github for projects, working with teams to push and pull code, fetch in JavaScript, Bootstrap, Jquery, mysql, api creating, file pathing, Webpack, React, and JSON implementation.
- Collaborated on building a website from scratch, utilizing fetch API, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. The website displays actual movie reviews and provides users with a separate page containing a movie synopsis when clicked.
- Collaborated on building a website from scratch, creating custom API routes for file integration. Utilized Handlebars for client-side display, MySQL for backend database storage, and implemented Tailwind CSS for styling.

Georgia State University | Bachelor of Computer Information System

May 2020

• GPA & Concentration: 3.5/4.0, Cyber Security

SKILLS

| Project Management | Client Facing Communication | Time Management | PowerBI | Microsoft Products | Data Manipulation | HTML | CSS | Javascript | MongoDB | API Calling | Github | GIT | JSON | NPM Packages | Mysql | WebPack | React |